（忆往昔）
这些从炼狱里跑出来的…
Those things from purgatory.
叫利维坦
Leviathan.
他们就像易形者 只是更爱吃人肉
They're like shapeshifters only a lot more into eating folk.
他们流出的是黑色的胶状物
And they bleed black goo.
辛格先生 我相信你肯定认识米尔斯警长
Mr. Singer. I believe you know sheriff mills.
是他妈的迪克·罗曼
It's Dick frigging Roman.
谁是他妈的迪克·罗曼
Who the hell is Dick frigging Roman?
我要吃了你 鲍比 没错
I'm gonna eat you, Bob. Yes.
鲍比 快
Bobby! Come on!
快 快
Come on! Come on!
快走
Go! Go!
鲍比 给你帽子
Hey, Bobby, your hat.
天啊 鲍比 坚持住
Oh, god. Bobby?! Hold on!
怎么 你来了结未完成的工作吗
What, did you come here to finish the job?
我们会来找你的
We're coming for you,
不只是要伤到你 而是要杀了你
and not just to hurt you … to kill you.
鲍比
Bobby…
谢谢你为我们做的一切
Thanks…for everything.
小混球
Idjits.
鲍比
Bobby?
（如今）
好了 行动吧 动作迅速点
All right, let's do this. Move fast.
等等 先说说我们的计划
Wait, wait, wait. What's the plan exactly?
保命
Don't die.
他朝市中心走了
He's heading downtown.
好了 你去大路包抄 我从小巷跟踪
All right, you take the street. I'll take the alley.
咱们在中间汇合
I'll meet you in the middle.
妈了个…
Son of a…
迪恩
Dean?
Dean?!
[邪恶力量 第7季第12集]
（两天前）
（金融市场观察 理查德·罗曼企业股指大幅上扬）
别一副「该换尿布了」的表情
Don't give me that dirty-diaper look.
又不是我打的
I ain't calling you.
喂
Hello?
萨姆 我是乔迪·米尔斯 吵醒你了吗
Sam, it's Jody Mills. I wake you?
警长
The sheriff?
是啊 我是说…
Yeah. Uh, I mean, uh …
我听说一件事 貌似跟你们有关
Listen, I got something that smells like you boys.
在俄州坎顿发现一具尸体
A body turned up in Canton, Ohio.
当地警方想把案子和尸体一起掩埋
Local P.D.'s trying to bury the story and the body.
好吧 那具尸体有什么问题
Okay, um, so, uh, what's up with the body?
死者失踪的时候
Well, when it went missing,
还是个很普通的研究生
it was a perfectly normal grad student.
叫查尔斯·德彬
named Charles Durbin.
尸体被发现的时候
When it turned up,
就像一具剥掉纱布的木乃伊
the thing was mummified minus the wrapping.
近两三周以来 类似形态的尸体
This is actually the second body found like this.
这已经是第二具了
in the last couple weeks.
听着像是你们在找的东西吗
Sound like a song you boys tap to?
对 没错 那…
Yeah, yeah, that's, that's um…
这就是我们该干的活儿
That's our kind of number.
我有个问题
Hey, question …
苏福尔斯（美国中北部）的警长
How does a sheriff in Sioux Falls.
怎么能听到俄州（美国南部）案子的风声
get wind of a case in Ohio?
我就是爱打听
I'm just that nosy.
我和你们哥俩经历过那么多事情之后
Look, after everything I've been through with you boys and…
还有鲍比
with bobby, you know,
我就对类似的事情格外留心
something like this pops up on the wire, it catches my ear.
没办法
What can I say?
我们会去查的 谢谢你 警长
Well, we'll look into it. Thanks, sheriff.
- 有消息给我电话 好吗 - 好的
- Call me after, okay? - Yeah.
是米尔斯警长 她帮我们找了桩活儿干
That was Sheriff Mills. She caught us one.
我觉得过意不去 咱们也没帮上她的忙
Oh, I feel bad. We didn't get her anything.
真不敢相信我要说这话
I can't believe I'm about to say this.
但我更希望你是在看色情卡通片
but I hope you're watching cartoon smut,
因为反复看迪克·罗曼那些破烂玩意
'cause reading Dick Roman crap over and over again.
简直就是自讨苦吃
is just self-punishment.
那叫日本动画 是种艺术形式
It's called Anime, and it's an art form.
（俄亥俄 坎顿）
这房子看着不错
Well, this looks nice.
去后面看看吧
Check around back?
楼上有个能凑合用的卫生间
Well, there's a semi-functioning bathroom.
还有个没有霉味的卧室
and one un-rancid bedroom.
什么叫能凑合用
Define semi-functioning,
别跟我说「地上有个坑」
and do not use the words "hole in the floor."
布凭什么就能击败石头
How does paper beat a rock.
这规则真傻逼
It's stupid.
玩捉迷藏的孩子发现了那具尸体
Kids playing hide-and-seek found the body.
挺有图特王（埃及法老）的范儿
Wow. Very King Tut.
是啊 目睹了袭击的目击证人
Yeah, so, this is where the eyewitness.
就住在这里
to the assault lives,
但警方觉得他的证词不可靠
but the cops are calling him an unreliable witness.
为什么
Because?
我们去问问看
Let's find out.
我是史密斯特工
Special Agent Smith.
这位是 史密斯特工
This is, uh, Special Agent Smith.
没有血缘关系
No relation.
我们出去谈好吗
Do you mind if we, uh…
我妈在里面睡觉
My mom's sleeping in there.
需要我怎么…
S-so, how can I…?
对于你在巷子里目击到的事件
Oh, we, uh … we had a few questions about the incident.
我们有几个问题
you witnessed in the alley.
你们会跟他们一样笑话我吧
You just gonna laugh at my story like the rest of the suits?
我们不会笑话你
We're not gonna laugh at you.
好吧 我当时在台阶上
All right, well, I'm on the steps…
抽大麻 然后听到有人打架
medicating… when I hear fighting.
我就看了看
So I look.
是我的邻居德彬
There's my neighbor Durbin,
有个打扮得像我爷爷的家伙
and some dude dressed like my grandpa's.
掐住了他的脖子
got him by the neck, right?
什么叫像你的爷爷
What do you he looks like your grandpa?
鞋子时髦 西装革履
Uh… snappy shoes, suit,
戴一顶贾斯汀·汀布莱克（美国歌手）的那种帽子
one of those, um, Justin Timberlake hats.
你是说一种毡帽
Y-you mean a … a fedora?
就是
Aha!
还有什么发现吗
Did you see anything else?
有种红色的能量
This red, like, energy.
从德彬传到了帽子男身上
passed through Durbin to hat guy.
连我的手表都停了
Even my watch stopped.
德比
Durbs…
我眼看着他变老了
He aged before my eyes.
变得皱巴巴的
He looked like a raisin.
我们相信你的话
Well, we believe you.
谢谢你的帮助
Thanks for your help.
谢谢警官 两位警官
Thank you, officer … officers.
没找到什么能把一个小伙子变成守墓人
Yep. Nothing that turns a dude into a crypt keeper.
你那边呢
You?
大坎顿地区貌似多次出现
Uh, well, greater Canton turns out kind of a hot spot.
怪异的死尸
for weird dead bodies.
是吗 不会吧
Hmm. You don't say.
真的 旧闻归档
Yeah. News archives.
但报道时并没说是风干成了木乃伊
They're not exactly reporting, uh, mummifies.
不过呢 1928年
But still … 1928,
三名死者貌似自燃
three deaths cited as spontaneous combustion.
尸体萎缩 但没有火烧痕迹
Bodies "Shriveled despite no signs of fire."
有点牵强 不过还好
Little stretch, but okay.
1974年 发现了三具皮肤萎缩的尸体
'74, three bodies found with leathery decay.
1957年 又有三具尸体严重脱水
Uh, '57, three more … severe dehydration.
这一次登了头版
This time one made the front page.
小女孩特里·塞万提斯在教堂附近发现尸体
Girl named Terry Cervantes found a corpse near her church.
除了地点以外还有什么规律可循吗
Any pattern here other than the location?
受害者和作案年份无规律
Random vics, random years.
不过死者似乎成三出现
But they seem to drop in threes.
现在有两个 还差一个
That's two down, one to go.
好吧 让我试试
All right, let me drive for a sec.
干嘛 你是要找动画片呢
What, are you gonna look up more anime,
还是要直接找迪克呢
or are you strictly into Dick now?
- 这是内部资料 - 对头
- Are those local feeds? - Yeah.
你怎么这么快就找出来了
How did you do that so fast?
弗兰克给我开了小灶
A little tutorial from Frank.
别担心 我们只当没发生过
Don't worry. We'll pretend this never happened.
干尸二号是在主街附近的
Now, mummy numero dos was found at the gas n' sip.
加油站发现的 对吧
near main street, correct?
对
Yeah.
好了 这是加油站周围所有的摄像头
All right, well, here's all the cameras around that store.
你得教我这一招
You need to teach me that trick.
看到了 汀布莱克
Hey, check it out … Timberlake.
等等
Wait a sec.
你就不能让我多得瑟一会儿吗
You can't let me bask in the glory for one second, can you?
闭嘴
Shut up.
看
Look.
他一点儿都没有变老 对吧
He hasn't aged a day, has he?
好吧 如果他几十年来都有露过面
All right, well, if he's been popping up for decades now,
那就肯定有人认识他 对吧
then somebody's bound to know who he is, right?
特里有没有可能还住在当地
Is there any chance that, uh, Terry's still local?
春天的景色非常漂亮
You know it's so pretty in the spring.
万物复苏
Everything's blooming.
所以我从那条路走回家
That's why I walked home that way …
看看沿途的花儿
to see the flowers.
结果看到的是那具尸体
Instead, I found that body.
我至今不明白 到底那人发生了什么事
I still have no idea what could have done that to a person.
你认识这个人吗
Do you recognize that man?
认得
Yeah.
他以前和我爸妈住一条街
I mean, he lived on my parents' street.
施耐德先生
Mr. Snider.
你爸妈具体住在哪里
Where'd you say your parents live?
这东西到底是什么
So, what exactly is this thing?
是个特别讨人嫌的吸血鬼吗
Some sort of vampire who got too sucky?
不会
Nope.
根据验尸报告 两具尸体内都有血液
Coroner's reports said there was blood in both bodies.
三百年的血 反正有血
300-year-old blood, but blood.
那家伙 戴毡帽的家伙
Dude, dude. Uh, fedora dude.
好了 行动吧
All right, let's do this.
动作迅速点
Let's move fast.
等等 先说说我们的计划
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What's the plan here, exactly?
报命
Don't die.
他朝市中心走了
He's heading downtown.
好了 你去大路包抄 我从小巷跟踪
All right, you take the street. I'll take the alley.
咱们在中间汇合
I'll meet you in the middle.
妈了个…
Son of a…
说你呢
Hey, you!
放下枪
Drop the gun!
放下 放下枪
Put it down! Drop the gun!
好
All right.
- 我能不能… - 闭嘴
- Okay, can I just … - Don't.
听我说
Listen to me.
如果你再说一遍你是从局里来的
Hey, if you tell me you're from the bureau one more time,
我就亲自揍扁你
I'm gonna air you out myself.
明白了吗
Got it?
「没信号」
"No signal."
你是不是什么骗子间谍
Are you some kind of Jerry spy?
什么骗子
Jerry who?
还是个水平不高的
And a terrible one at that.
这个证件的签发日期是六十八年后
This badge was issued 68 years from now.
干得不错啊 德国佬
Ace work, Kraut Muncher.
四四年
'44?
我被困在1944年了吗
I'm stuck in 1944?!
我们都困在1944年 小杂种
We're all stuck in 1944, ya bunny.
你先出去一下
Take a powder.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
我根本都不喜欢德国泡菜 好吗
Look I don't even like frigging sauerkraut, okay,
所以你能不能省了那套…
so you can just skip the …
小巷里到底发生什么事了 给我讲清楚
What happened in the alley? And paint me a real picture.
好吧
All right, well,
不管我说什么都像疯话 还是说吧
I'm "12 monkey'ed" no matter what I say, so here goes.
我在追一个家伙 刚看见他把一个人吸成干尸
I was chasing this dude. Uh, I'd just seen him mummify a guy.
是啊 所以我突袭了他
Yeah. So, I jumped him.
他发出红光 一下子我们就到了1944年
He lights up red. Poof, we're in 1944.
跟我再说说那红光
Tell me more about the red light.
你真的在问我…
Are you seriously asking …
你要是还想出这监狱
You want out of this jail,
你就如实告诉我关于那人的情况
you're gonna tell me everything you can about that man.
还有你所谓的红光
and the so-called light.
好吧
Okay.
我看见了 然后我们就到这儿了
I saw it, and then we were here.
你是说…那光环绕着你吗
Would you say that, uh… it was all around you.
还是从那家伙体内放射出来的
or that more that it came from inside this fella?
你相信我的话
You believe me.
你是…
Are you…?
你是个猎人
You're a hunter.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
恶魔 鬼魂 异形者
Demons, ghosts, shifters.
这些我都杀过
Hey, I've killed 'em all.
而你和我是一类人
And you're the same,
只是比我早六十八年 对吧
just 68 years before me, huh?
你是…
And your name is…?
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean Winchester.
我是尼斯
Ness.
爱略特·尼斯
Eliot Ness.
迪恩
Dean?
不是的 怎么了 迪恩哪去了
No. Why? Where's Dean?
那个能把人吸成干尸的东西
The thing that's been mummifying people.
把他劫到一个光球里了 然后就消失了
took him in a frigging ball of light and disappeared.
你们经常碰到这种情况吗
You guys get that a lot?
是 比常人多些
Yeah, more than most people.
是我给你们找的这事 所以…
Well, I got you into this, so …
不 不 不是你 你只不过…
No, no, no, you didn't. A-all you did was just …
闭嘴 萨姆
Shut up, Sam.
我能帮什么忙
How I can help?
那你愿意搬搬箱子 拉拉货吗
Well, um… How do you feel about driving and lifting boxes?
我得跟你说 《铁面无私》是…
I-I got to tell you, I mean, "Untouchables" is, like,
我最喜欢的电影之一
one of my most favorite movies ever.
- 什么 - 我看了不下五十遍
- What? - I must have seen that thing, like, 50 times.
「看过」 你是说我出现在…
"Seen it?" what, like, I'm in the …
对了 你都不知道 你简直太牛逼了
Oh, yeah, yeah! You don't even know! Oh, you are …!
等等 等等 咱们慢点说
Look, hey, wait, wait, wait. Let's just…slow it down.
好吗
Okay?
现在先说时光旅行
Now, time travel.
这是不是在你们那个时代
is that something you find up a lot of sleeves.
已经很普及了…
in the future or…?
不 不 在我们那个时代这也不正常
No, no, no. It's, uh, not normally on the menu.
相信我 我跟你一样惊讶
Trust me. I'm as surprised as you are that I'm here.
但我们是在追捕同样的东西
So we're hunting the same thing,
只是在不同的年代
just in different centuries?
我这儿死了两个人
Two bodies.
是在一个多月前 中间差了几天
A few days apart just a little over a month ago.
一个目击者说她看见那歹徒
One witness said that she saw an assailant.
在风干受害者生命之后发出红光
light up red after sucking the life out of a man.
酷
Awesome.
你怎么会对此心生敬畏呢
How does that fill you with awe?
迪恩 这东西
Look, Dean, this thing, it kills …
- 一次杀三人 - 一次杀三人
- In threes. - in threes.
你已经知道了
But you already know that.
他已经杀了两人
He's two down.
你跟我走
You're coming with me.
我们得在他再杀一个人前抓住他
We've got to get this thing before it grabs the last one.
等等
So, wait, uh…
就是说我现在是个铁面探员了吗
Does…does this mean that I'm an Untouchable now?
就是说我们得去给你换些新衣服
It means we got to get you into some new clothes.
你看起来就跟流浪汉似的
You look like some kind of bindle stiff.
流 啥
Stiff your br… bin… what?
有什么事 爱略特
What's the rumpus, Eliot?
这是埃兹拉·摩尔 这是迪恩·温彻斯特
Ezra moore. Dean winchester.
他是谁 乡下人吗
Who's he? Some farmer clown?
他 来自未来
He's, uh, from the future.
天然气四块钱
Yeah. Gas costs four bucks.
喷雾罐能挤出奶酪
You can get cheese out of a spray can.
还有 总理是个黑人
And…the president, he's a black guy.
我还能继续往下说
I could go on.
真让我开眼啊
Paint me impressed.
我估计你需要些新衣服
I assume you need some clothes.
来吧
Come on.
我来 我来帮你拿吧
Hey, let me, uh … let me help you with those.
不用了 我可以的
No, I got these.
你去把我车里另外二十箱搬来
You go get the other 20 in my truck.
不是吧
Seriously?
是的
Yeah.
我觉得鲍比可能有点轻微的囤积症
I think Bobby may have had a slight hoarding issue.
我差点打不开储存柜的门
I could barely get the door open on that storage locker.
还有 我很肯定至少有三箱
And, um, I'm pretty sure something's alive.
里面是有活物的
in at least three of those boxes.
酷
Awesome.
「令人敬畏」 你是信教的怪人吗
"Awesome"? You some religious kook?
不 他只是喜欢这么说
No, he just likes saying that.
话说在前头
So, spill already.
你们两个笨蛋又趟了什么浑水呢
What bucket of syrup did you two idjits step into?
很好笑吗 甜心
Something funny, sweetheart?
不是 你
No, you, uh…
你让我想起了一个人
You just kind of remind me of someone.
埃兹拉 我们需要你帮忙
Okay, Ezra… we need your help.
貌似我们俩是在猎杀一个时间旅行者
It seems we're hunting a time traveler.
真不错
Delightful.
（联邦犯罪数据库 安全服务器）
查到了
Got it.
那个 他手指上的那个是只戒指吗
Is that a … is that a ring on his finger?
没错
Yeah.
我见过这个符号
I know that symbol.
这是个无垠沙漏
It's the Infinite Hourglass.
这就是我在他戒指上看到的符号
That's the symbol I saw on his ring.
- 这是时间神的标志 - 谁
- Yeah, that's the mark of Chronos. - Who?
时间之神
The God of Time.
太疯狂了
That's crazy.
事情是这样的 那些上古之神
The thing is, with the Old Gods,
从前他们 他们还不是天下无敌的
once upon a time they were… they were just short of invincible.
但他们的魔力大多来自他们的崇拜者
But they got a lot of their mojo from worshippers,
那些进贡他们的人
from people feeding them.
而如今 很少有这种人了
These days, not so much.
没错 他们没有以前强大了
Right, they're not what they used to be.
但他们用翻倍的怒气
But they make up for lack of power.
以及亲自动手来弥补了力量的不足
with being twice as pissed and a lot more hands-on.
好吧
Ok.
那这位神为什么要杀人
So why's this God killing people?
他杀人可能是为了恢复能量
Could be he's killing folks for his time juice.
好吧 那我到底要怎么
All right, well, how the hell.
让他捎我回到2012年呢
am I gonna ride him back to 2012?
你可以让他抓着你
Well, you could let him grab you,
如果你不介意他把你当做汽油用的话
if you don't mind him using you for gasoline.
那我们怎么把迪恩带回来
So, how do we get Dean back?
怎么找到这个时间神呢
How do we even find this Chronos?
最好的办法
Best stab?
我们找出一个召唤神的方法
We find a way to summon a God.
我们还是先说我们知道事情吧
Look, let's just stick with what we know.
埃兹拉 试试看你能否在这堆破东西里
Ezra, see if you can find something in all this junk.
找出什么是能杀死神的
that will kill a God.
完全没问题
No trouble at all.
几小时后过来 看我能弄到什么
Come in a few hours, see what I can scrounge up.
你说你们找到他家了
You said you fellas found his house?
我们去看看他家现在建成了没有
Well, let's go see if it's been built yet.
然后我们就杀了那个混蛋 因为这
And then let's kill that bastard, because that …
就是芝加哥的范儿
is the Chicago way.
「芝加哥的范儿」
"The chicago way?"
谁会这样讲话啊
Who talks like that?
肖恩·康纳利
Sean Connery.
过来
Come on.
再也不要看那部电影了
Never watch that movie again.
- 好像没人 你带开锁器了吗 - 当然
- It looks empty. You got a lock pick? - Sure.
四处看看
Take a look around.
他哪来的钱能供得起这些
Where's he getting all the lettuce to support this?
他在用「重拳出击」战略
He's using the "biff strategy."
用什么
Using what?
时间神在赌那些
Chronos is betting on races.
他早已知道结果的比赛
he already knows the outcome of.
看看这个
Look at this.
他在1944年呆的挺长
He's spent a lot of time in '44.
L.Y.是什么东西
What's L.Y.?
那不是东西 是人 叫莱斯特·扬
It's not a what. It's a who. Lester Young.
他给镇上的混混们投注
He lays bets for a lot of the flunkies in town.
我们去会会他
Let's say we go pay him a visit.
别毁了我的夹克
Hey! Hey! Easy with the jacket!
我可不会说的
Yeah, I ain't talking.
我又不是你的探子
I'm no stoolie.
这招是跟你学来的
I learned it from watching you.
你是个聪明人 莱斯特
Look, you seem like a swell guy, Lester.
我很想帮你一把 但我的搭档
And I want to help you out. I do, but my partner here?
刚从战场上回来
He just back from the war.
过去两年
And he's spent the last two years.
他都在痛扁纳粹
kicking in Nazi's skulls.
如果几天不揍人
If he doesn't kick in a skull every couple days,
他就会手痒了
He gets real touchy.
莱斯特是个德语名字吗
Lester. That a German name?
好吧
Hey, okay, okay.
别激动嘛
There's no need to snap your cap.
你们想找谁
W-who you looking for?
一个叫施耐德的小伙子
Fella by the name of Snider.
那个家伙
What, that guy?
他从不错过赌局
I mean, bum never missed a bet,
但老让我浑身不舒服
but he gave me the heebie-jeebies,
所以我把他踢了
So I cut him off.
你在哪里付钱给他
Where would you meet him for the payoff?
在早起之鸟 海格提的一个破餐馆
T-the early bird! It's a dive on Haggerty.
他几乎就住在那一带
Practically lives in the joint.
- 该死 - 找到了
- Damn it - That's it!
看来你有好消息 说吧
Okay, yours sounds better. You first.
这里说人们可以召唤时间神
It says here that people could summon Chronos.
「要求其预言他们的未来」
"to compel him to tell them their futures."
我找到了召唤它的咒语
And I've got the spell to do it right here.
那你怎么叫「该死」
So why the "Damn it"?
召唤时间神不是问题
'cause calling Chronos isn't the problem.
但召唤的时候
It's making sure we summon him.
迪恩得在他旁边
when Dean is right there…
严格地说要把手放那家伙身上
Literally with his hands on the guy,
就能跟着他一起回来了
so he can surf him back.
不是自动就能回来吗
That's not automatic?
不是 我们需要找准他们那边的时间
No, it's more like we need to get the time on their end right.
差一秒都不行
To the exact second.
不然回来的就是愤怒的大神而不是你哥了
Or we get an angry god but no big brother?
而我哥就永远困那儿了
And he's trapped there forever.
「混蛋 你赢了 享用吧 R」
"Fine, you ass. You win for once. Enjoy. R."
谁是「R」
Who's "R"?
鲁弗斯 家里一个朋友
Rufus, a family friend.
不知道他们打的什么赌
Wonder what they were betting over?
不管是什么 鲁弗斯输得很不甘心啊
Well, whatever it was, Rufus sure was a sore loser.
挺奇怪的 是吧
It's weird, huh?
他们的生活像个拼图
It's like their life's a big puzzle.
你总是能到处找到它的碎片
You just keep finding pieces of it scattered all over the place.
我们应该喝了它
We should drink this.
他会希望如此 我说的对吗
He'd want us to. Am I wrong?
不喝才没品
It'd be rude not to.
就是他
That's him.
对一个神来说他有点弱
Kind of puny for a god.
我还以为你是个正派先生呢
Thought you were, uh … thought you were Mr. Boy scout.
你觉得我当初是为什么要去追查卡蓬（芝加哥黑手党老大）
Why do you think I went after Capone in the first place?
因为他藏有芝加哥最好的酒
The guy had the best hooch in Chicago.
你因为谁的死做了猎魔人
So, now, w-who died in your life and made you a hunter?
谁的死 没人挂了 变态
Who died? Nobody died, you morbid son of a bitch.
我从事这行
I started doing this.
是因为吸血鬼在克利夫兰转化人
'cause vampires were turning folks in Cleveland.
然后你就猎上瘾了
And you got the bug.
没错 然后我就上瘾了
That's when I got the bug.
有时候我就想用银弹
Sometimes you just want to punch through the red tape.
崩了官场缛节
with a silver bullet.
猎魔让我自由 你难道不是因为这个
Yeah, hunting sets me free. Isn't that why you hunt?
以前我猎魔是因为家族传统
I used to do it 'cause that's what my family did.
但他们还是接二连三的死了
But they just seem to keep dying.
老实说吧
To tell you the truth,
我都不知道做这些事为了什么
I don't know why I'm doing much of anything anymore.
你打算《泪流成河》吗 娘娘腔
Boo-hoo. Cry me a river, ya Nancy.
未来的猎魔人都像你这样多愁善感吗
Tell me, are all hunters as soft as you in the future?
每个人都会失去家人 直到有一天
Everybody loses everybody. And then one day, boom.
轮到你了 但你至少做了一番贡献
Your number's up, but at least you're making a difference.
趁你还活着享受生活吧 小子
So enjoy it while it lasts, kid,
因为猎魔是你生活中
'cause hunting's the only clarity.
唯一丁是丁卯是卯的东西
you're gonna find in this life.
所以你比大多数人要幸运
And that makes you luckier than most.
你好啊 护士
Hello, nurse.
太酷了
Sweet merciful awesome.
有头绪了 小子
Well, everything's coming up us, kid.
说说看
Talk to me.
我正在说呢
I am.
房主莉拉·泰勒小姐 芳龄二十
The owner of the house, Miss Lila Taylor, age 20,
一个人住
lives alone.
你开车去找埃兹拉 看看她查到了什么
Take the car, head back to Ezra, see what she's got.
我就待在这里
I'm gonna stay here.
继续监视这对小夫妻
and keep my peepers on the sheik and the sheba.
就那个
That's it?
那可是维斯太贞女用千年的橄榄树枝雕刻
That is a 1, 000-year-old olive carved by vestal virgins.
并浸蘸了你不会想知道的某种血液
and dipped in the blood of … you don't want to know.
找到这个可不是容易的事
Pulling this together wasn't easy.
你和尼斯都欠我个人情 亲爱的
You and Ness both owe me, smoothie.
等我们抓到那家伙你就可以得到你想要的了
You can have whatever you want soon as we gank this thing.
是啊是啊 带上你的嫩枝 聪明蛋
Yeah, yeah. Take your twig, wise guy.
那 这个怎么用
Well, now, how's it work?
你要将这头刺入他的心脏
You stick this end in his heart.
没中 你就变成他的晚餐
Miss, he has you for supper.
明白了吗
Make sense?
等等 如果我
Wait, if I …
如果我杀了时间神 我就被困在这里了
If I kill chronos… I'm stuck here.
你才意识到吗
You just now realized?
1944年没那么糟糕啦
Oh, come on. 1944 ain't so bad.
是啊 我可以冲去欧洲
Yeah, I could head over to Europe,
打断希特勒的脖子
punch Hitler in the neck.
消磨时光的方法太多了 小甜心
Oh, there's lots of ways to pass the time, sugar.
祝你好运
That's for luck.
因为我很幸运
'Cause I'm lucky.
谢谢
Thanks.
《回到未来3》
"Back to the future iii."
我要借张纸
I need to borrow some paper.
我想 你是尼斯先生吧
Mr. Ness I presume?
你知道 我之前去警局
You know, I stopped by the police station.
想了结跟着我过来的那个猎人
to take care of that hunter who rode me here.
我听说你把他从监狱里放出来了
I heard you took him out of jail.
我就想我也许能再见到你
I thought I might see you again.
伊森
Ethan?
你在这儿啊
There you are.
傻瓜 没带垃圾怎么能倒垃圾呢
Can't take the trash out without the trash, silly.
抱歉 亲爱的
Sorry, honey.
真不知道脑子丢在哪了
I don't know where I left my head.
马上就去
Be right there.
亲爱的 我希望你收拾一下行李
Sweetie, I want you to pack a bag.
什么
Excuse me?
你一直问我我去哪
Well, you're always asking me where I go.
今晚和我一起走吧
Come with me tonight.
没出什么事吧
Is…is everything okay?
没事 一切都很好
Yeah, everything's perfect.
你太好了
You're perfect.
你赶紧收拾行李吧
I just need you to pack a bag.
我会在路上告诉你原因的 好吗
and I'll explain why on the way, okay?
- 但是餐馆… - 别管他们
- But the diner… - Forget about them!
明天给他们打电话 好吗
We'll call them tomorrow, okay?
去吧 收拾
Just go. Pack.
找到了
Jackpot.
有事吗 孩子
Can I help you, son?
是的 先生 我是特别探员寇斯纳
Yes, sir. I am, uh, special agent Costner.
我是国家白蚁防治部的
with the, uh, department of homeland termite invasion.
- 白蚁 - 是的
- Termites? - Yes, sir.
本区域爆发了白蚁灾害
There's been an outbreak all over this area,
所以我需要检查一下
and I just want to do an inspection,
确保这一带的安全
make sure that the, uh, perimeter's secure.
是吗 好啊 请进吧
Yes. Yes, of course. Um, you'd better come in.
好的
Okay.
这里没什么问题吧
Is everything okay up here?
什么
What?!
是的 没问题
Oh, yeah … no!
没有
No, no.
别担心 因为我正要帮你安装
Not to worry, because I'm going to install something.
能永远保护这屋子的东西
that will protect this house forever.
好吧
Yeah.
你累坏了吧
You are toast.
我继续跟进 你去休息一会
I'll keep pushing. You go get some shut-eye.
没事 我能
Uh, that's okay. I can, uh…
要我搬出妈妈的威严吗
Do I have to use my mom voice?
（萨姆）
好吧 你自找的
All right. You asked for it.
年轻人
Young man …
「小萨姆 事实证明施耐德就是时间神」
"Sammy, turns out Snider is chronos."
等下 这是迪恩写的 怎么
Wait, this is from Dean? How …
继续看
Just read.
「我跟着他回到了1944年
"I rode him to 1944.
和爱略特·尼斯一起 没错 就是那个
Am working with Eliot Ness … yes, that one.
找到了时间神
Tracked down chronos.
他正和一个名叫莉拉·泰勒的妞交往
He's banging some chick named Lila Taylor,
我们拿到了武器
and we got a weapon.
我们要去追捕他 萨姆 你保重「
We're going after him. Take care of yourself, Sam."
- 看信首 - 1944年11月5日
- Look at the top. - November 5, '44.
所以现在我们知道了迪恩
So, now we know the exact date.
抓住时间神的确切日期
Dean had hands on chronos.
现在我们只需要知道确切的时间
All we need is the exact time.
怎么才能知道
Which we get how?
希望 我们能问问当时在场的人
Hoping, we ask someone who was there.
莉拉·泰勒小姐吗
Miss Lila Taylor?
你能给我调出《小城名流》吗
Oh, can you get "The Sullivan Show"?
我想看弗兰基·瓦力
I want to watch that Frankie Valli.
事实上 我们是警察
Um, actually, we're with the police.
迈克尔又闯祸了吗
Is Michael in trouble again?
早就叫他别看那些漫画书了
I told him not to read those comic books.
不 不 不 他…他没事
Uh, no, no, no, no. He's, uh … he's fine.
我们来是想问问这个人的情况
We'd wanted to ask you some questions about this man.
伊森
Ethan.
这是伊森
That's Ethan.
你还记得上一次见他是什么时候吗
Do you remember the last time you saw Ethan?
当然
Of course.
1944年11月
November 1944 …
时钟停止摆动的那个晚上
the night the clocks stopped.
时钟停止摆动了吗
Th-the clocks stopped?
11点34分 屋里的所有时钟无一例外
11:34. Every clock in the house.
女士 你还记得什么其他情况吗
Ma'am, can you tell us anything else you remember?
伊森…
Ethan…
说了些不堪入耳的话
said awful things.
然后…
And then…
然后他掐死了那个可怜的小伙子
And then he strangled that poor man.
什么可怜的小伙子
What poor man?
两个警察过来想要逮捕伊森
Two policemen came to arrest Ethan.
女士 这个人是不是其中之一
Ma'am, was this one of them?
伊森把这人活活的掐死了
Ethan choked the life out of that man.
尼斯
Ness!
伊森
Ethan!
我们谈谈
Let's talk.
把这个砸碎
Here, break this.
请别伤害她
Please don't hurt her.
伊森 出什么事了
Ethan, what's happening?
是啊 伊森 怎么回事
Yeah, Ethan. What the hell?
莉拉 抱歉 但你…
Lila, I'm sorry, but, you just …
我对你说过的每句话都是真心实意的…
Everything I said to you is true…
他也许只是省略了一些细枝末节
Oh, he might have left out a few details.
比如 他是个能穿越时空的怪物
He tells you he's a monster who jumps through time?
哥是神
I'm a god!
听着 我不是什么怪物
Look, I'm not a monster.
听我说 恰恰相反
Listen. I'm the opposite.
你这小子太健忘了吧 说说
Well, don't forget to tell her about.
- 你这一路走来杀了多少人吧 - 什么
- all the people you murdered along the way, Boy Scout. - What?
不是你想的那样
It's not like that.
我为了你才这么做 莉拉
I do it for you, Lila.
我不明白
I don't understand.
他的力量每况愈下
Well, he's not as strong as he used to be.
难道不是吗 伊森
Isn't that right, Ethan?
你为了获取能力必须吸干他人的能量
Now you got to grew up and suck people dry.
不妨让我猜猜 三次杀戮能让你原地复活
Wild guess … it takes three kills to juice you up.
那叫祭品
Sacrifices.
三个祭品
Three sacrifices,
能让我控制穿越的时间和地点
and I can control when and where I land.
但我到了一地 总是不能久留
But once I get there, it's never for long.
很快又被抛到另一个时间里
before I'm tossed through time again.
这就是我的生活 莉拉
That's my life, Lila.
我所要的不过是回到这儿
And all I want is to get back here.
是因为你爱上了坎顿的清新空气吗
Because you just love the clean Canton air?
因为我爱她
Because I love her!
因为我的生活如炼狱一般
Because I lived the worst existence you can imagine,
直到遇见了你
and then I found you.
在你杀害了泰勒·克罗斯比
After you killed Tyler Crosby.
和凯茜·波特之后
and Cathy Porter?
莉拉原本即将成为第三位受害者
Lila here was gonna be victim No.3.
我没说错吧
Am I right?
老兄 别装作一副遇到她之前
Don't act like you never killed a soul.
好像从未杀过人的样子
before you met her, pal.
我觉得过去你为了换个风景
Something tells me you used to kill three saps.
都会对三条人命下手
just for a change of scenery.
没错 是的
Yes, I did.
退后
Back down.
我…我过去漫无目的地游荡
I-I used to wander,
但现在我有你为伴
but now I have you.
我认识凯茜
I knew Cathy.
她以前每天都来餐馆
She used to come into the diner every day.
莉拉 别这样
Lila, please.
你是个怪物
You are a monster.
不 莉拉 求你了
No, Lila, please!
[咒语]
不
No!
铁面探员
Hey, untouchable!
迪恩
Dean!
不
No!
你个混蛋 毁了一切
You! Destroyed everything!
时间神
Hey, Chronos?!
你就这点本事吗
Was that the best you got?
你想知道你的未来吗
You want to know your future?
我知道你的未来
I know your future.
被一片黑色浓胶状物覆盖
It's covered in thick black ooze.
遍地都是
It's everywhere.
他们无处不在
They're everywhere.
希望你们喜欢被淹没
Enjoy oblivion.